<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><sst xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/spreadsheetml/2006/main" count="1352" uniqueCount="467"><si><t>Questions by Love Babbar:</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Youtube Channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCQHLxxBFrbfdrk1jF0moTpw </t></si><si><t>Topic:</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Problem: </t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Done [yes or no] </t></si><si><t>&lt;-&gt;</t></si><si><t>Array</t></si><si><t>Reverse the array</t></si><si><t>Yes</t></si><si><t>Find the maximum and minimum element in an array</t></si><si><t>yes</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Find the &quot;Kth&quot; max and min element of an array </t></si><si><t>Given an array which consists of only 0, 1 and 2. Sort the array without using any sorting algo</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Move all the negative elements to one side of the array </t></si><si><t>Find the Union and Intersection of the two sorted arrays.</t></si><si><t>Write a program to cyclically rotate an array by one.</t></si><si><t>find Largest sum contiguous Subarray [V. IMP]</t></si><si><t>Minimise the maximum difference between heights [V.IMP]</t></si><si><t>Minimum no. of Jumps to reach end of an array</t></si><si><t>find duplicate in an array of N+1 Integers</t></si><si><t>Merge 2 sorted arrays without using Extra space.</t></si><si><t>Kadane's Algo [V.V.V.V.V IMP]</t></si><si><t>Merge Intervals</t></si><si><t>Next Permutation</t></si><si><t>Count Inversion</t></si><si><t>Best time to buy and Sell stock</t></si><si><t>find all pairs on integer array whose sum is equal to given number</t></si><si><t>find common elements In 3 sorted arrays</t></si><si><t>Rearrange the array in alternating positive and negative items with O(1) extra space</t></si><si><t>Find if there is any subarray with sum equal to 0</t></si><si><t>Find factorial of a large number</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">find maximum product subarray </t></si><si><t>Find longest coinsecutive subsequence</t></si><si><t>Given an array of size n and a number k, fin all elements that appear more than &quot; n/k &quot; times.</t></si><si><t>Maximum profit by buying and selling a share atmost twice</t></si><si><t>Find whether an array is a subset of another array</t></si><si><t>Find the triplet that sum to a given value</t></si><si><t>Trapping Rain water problem</t></si><si><t>Chocolate Distribution problem</t></si><si><t>Smallest Subarray with sum greater than a given value</t></si><si><t>Three way partitioning of an array around a given value</t></si><si><t>Minimum swaps required bring elements less equal K together</t></si><si><t>Minimum no. of operations required to make an array palindrome</t></si><si><t>Median of 2 sorted arrays of equal size</t></si><si><t>Median of 2 sorted arrays of different size</t></si><si><t>Matrix</t></si><si><t>Spiral traversal on a Matrix</t></si><si><t>Search an element in a matriix</t></si><si><t>Find median in a row wise sorted matrix</t></si><si><t>Find row with maximum no. of 1's</t></si><si><t>Print elements in sorted order using row-column wise sorted matrix</t></si><si><t>Maximum size rectangle</t></si><si><t>Find a specific pair in matrix</t></si><si><t>Rotate matrix by 90 degrees</t></si><si><t>Kth smallest element in a row-cpumn wise sorted matrix</t></si><si><t>Common elements in all rows of a given matrix</t></si><si><t>String</t></si><si><t>Reverse a String</t></si><si><t>Check whether a String is Palindrome or not</t></si><si><t>Find Duplicate characters in a string</t></si><si><t>Why strings are immutable in Java?</t></si><si><t>Write a Code to check whether one string is a rotation of another</t></si><si><t>Write a Program to check whether a string is a valid shuffle of two strings or not</t></si><si><t>Count and Say problem</t></si><si><t>Write a program to find the longest Palindrome in a string.[ Longest palindromic Substring]</t></si><si><t>Find Longest Recurring Subsequence in String</t></si><si><t>Print all Subsequences of a string.</t></si><si><t>Print all the permutations of the given string</t></si><si><t>Split the Binary string into two substring with equal 0’s and 1’s</t></si><si><t>Word Wrap Problem [VERY IMP].</t></si><si><t>EDIT Distance [Very Imp]</t></si><si><t>Find next greater number with same set of digits. [Very Very IMP]</t></si><si><t>Balanced Parenthesis problem.[Imp]</t></si><si><t>Word break Problem[ Very Imp]</t></si><si><t>Rabin Karp Algo</t></si><si><t>KMP Algo</t></si><si><t>Convert a Sentence into its equivalent mobile numeric keypad sequence.</t></si><si><t>Minimum number of bracket reversals needed to make an expression balanced.</t></si><si><t>Count All Palindromic Subsequence in a given String.</t></si><si><t>Count of number of given string in 2D character array</t></si><si><t>Search a Word in a 2D Grid of characters.</t></si><si><t>Boyer Moore Algorithm for Pattern Searching.</t></si><si><t>Converting Roman Numerals to Decimal</t></si><si><t>Longest Common Prefix</t></si><si><t>Number of flips to make binary string alternate</t></si><si><t>Find the first repeated word in string.</t></si><si><t>Minimum number of swaps for bracket balancing.</t></si><si><t>Find the longest common subsequence between two strings.</t></si><si><t>Program to generate all possible valid IP addresses from given  string.</t></si><si><t>Write a program tofind the smallest window that contains all characters of string itself.</t></si><si><t>Rearrange characters in a string such that no two adjacent are same</t></si><si><t>Minimum characters to be added at front to make string palindrome</t></si><si><t>Given a sequence of words, print all anagrams together</t></si><si><t>Find the smallest window in a string containing all characters of another string</t></si><si><t>Recursively remove all adjacent duplicates</t></si><si><t>String matching where one string contains wildcard characters</t></si><si><t>Function to find Number of customers who could not get a computer</t></si><si><t>Transform One String to Another using Minimum Number of Given Operation</t></si><si><t>Check if two given strings are isomorphic to each other</t></si><si><t>Recursively print all sentences that can be formed from list of word lists</t></si><si><t>Searching &amp; Sorting</t></si><si><t>Find first and last positions of an element in a sorted array</t></si><si><t>Find a Fixed Point (Value equal to index) in a given array</t></si><si><t>Search in a rotated sorted array</t></si><si><t>square root of an integer</t></si><si><t>Maximum and minimum of an array using minimum number of comparisons</t></si><si><t>Optimum location of point to minimize total distance</t></si><si><t>Find the repeating and the missing</t></si><si><t>find majority element</t></si><si><t>Searching in an array where adjacent differ by at most k</t></si><si><t>find a pair with a given difference</t></si><si><t>find four elements that sum to a given value</t></si><si><t>maximum sum such that no 2 elements are adjacent</t></si><si><t>Count triplet with sum smaller than a given value</t></si><si><t>merge 2 sorted arrays</t></si><si><t>print all subarrays with 0 sum</t></si><si><t>Product array Puzzle</t></si><si><t>Sort array according to count of set bits</t></si><si><t>minimum no. of swaps required to sort the array</t></si><si><t>Bishu and Soldiers</t></si><si><t>Rasta and Kheshtak</t></si><si><t>Kth smallest number again</t></si><si><t>Find pivot element in a sorted array</t></si><si><t>K-th Element of Two Sorted Arrays</t></si><si><t>Aggressive cows</t></si><si><t>Book Allocation Problem</t></si><si><t>EKOSPOJ:</t></si><si><t>Job Scheduling Algo</t></si><si><t>Missing Number in AP</t></si><si><t>Smallest number with atleastn trailing zeroes infactorial</t></si><si><t>Painters Partition Problem:</t></si><si><t>ROTI-Prata SPOJ</t></si><si><t>DoubleHelix SPOJ</t></si><si><t>Subset Sums</t></si><si><t>Findthe inversion count</t></si><si><t>Implement Merge-sort in-place</t></si><si><t>Partitioning and Sorting Arrays with Many Repeated Entries</t></si><si><t>LinkedList</t></si><si><t>Write a Program to reverse the Linked List. (Both Iterative and recursive)</t></si><si><t>Reverse a Linked List in group of Given Size. [Very Imp]</t></si><si><t>Write a program to Detect loop in a linked list.</t></si><si><t>Write a program to Delete loop in a linked list.</t></si><si><t>Find the starting point of the loop. </t></si><si><t>Remove Duplicates in a sorted Linked List.</t></si><si><t>Remove Duplicates in a Un-sorted Linked List.</t></si><si><t>Write a Program to Move the last element to Front in a Linked List.</t></si><si><t>Add “1” to a number represented as a Linked List.</t></si><si><t>Add two numbers represented by linked lists.</t></si><si><t>Intersection of two Sorted Linked List.</t></si><si><t>Intersection Point of two Linked Lists.</t></si><si><t>Merge Sort For Linked lists.[Very Important]</t></si><si><t>Quicksort for Linked Lists.[Very Important]</t></si><si><t>Find the middle Element of a linked list.</t></si><si><t>Check if a linked list is a circular linked list.</t></si><si><t>Split a Circular linked list into two halves.</t></si><si><t>Write a Program to check whether the Singly Linked list is a palindrome or not.</t></si><si><t>Deletion from a Circular Linked List.</t></si><si><t>Reverse a Doubly Linked list.</t></si><si><t>Find pairs with a given sum in a DLL.</t></si><si><t>Count triplets in a sorted DLL whose sum is equal to given value “X”.</t></si><si><t>Sort a “k”sorted Doubly Linked list.[Very IMP]</t></si><si><t>Rotate DoublyLinked list by N nodes.</t></si><si><t>Rotate a Doubly Linked list in group of Given Size.[Very IMP]</t></si><si><t>Can we reverse a linked list in less than O(n) ?</t></si><si><t>Why Quicksort is preferred for. Arrays and Merge Sort for LinkedLists ?</t></si><si><t>Flatten a Linked List</t></si><si><t>Sort a LL of 0's, 1's and 2's</t></si><si><t>Clone a linked list with next and random pointer</t></si><si><t>Merge K sorted Linked list</t></si><si><t>Multiply 2 no. represented by LL</t></si><si><t>Delete nodes which have a greater value on right side</t></si><si><t>Segregate even and odd nodes in a Linked List</t></si><si><t>Program for n’th node from the end of a Linked List</t></si><si><t>Find the first non-repeating character from a stream of characters</t></si><si><t>Binary Trees</t></si><si><t>level order traversal</t></si><si><t>Reverse Level Order traversal</t></si><si><t>Height of a tree</t></si><si><t>Diameter of a tree</t></si><si><t>Mirror of a tree</t></si><si><t>Inorder Traversal of a tree both using recursion and Iteration</t></si><si><t>Preorder Traversal of a tree both using recursion and Iteration</t></si><si><t>Postorder Traversal of a tree both using recursion and Iteration</t></si><si><t>Left View of a tree</t></si><si><t>Right View of Tree</t></si><si><t>Top View of a tree</t></si><si><t>Bottom View of a tree</t></si><si><t>Zig-Zag traversal of a binary tree</t></si><si><t>Check if a tree is balanced or not</t></si><si><t>Diagnol Traversal of a Binary tree</t></si><si><t>Boundary traversal of a Binary tree</t></si><si><t>Construct Binary Tree from String with Bracket Representation</t></si><si><t>Convert Binary tree into Doubly Linked List</t></si><si><t>Convert Binary tree into Sum tree</t></si><si><t>Construct Binary tree from Inorder and preorder traversal</t></si><si><t>Find minimum swaps required to convert a Binary tree into BST</t></si><si><t>Check if Binary tree is Sum tree or not</t></si><si><t>Check if all leaf nodes are at same level or not</t></si><si><t>Check if a Binary Tree contains duplicate subtrees of size 2 or more [ IMP ]</t></si><si><t>Check if 2 trees are mirror or not</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Sum of Nodes on the Longest path from root to leaf node </t></si><si><t>Check if given graph is tree or not.  [ IMP ]</t></si><si><t>Find Largest subtree sum in a tree</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Maximum Sum of nodes in Binary tree such that no two are adjacent </t></si><si><t>Print all &quot;K&quot; Sum paths in a Binary tree</t></si><si><t>Find LCA in a Binary tree</t></si><si><t>Find distance between 2 nodes in a Binary tree</t></si><si><t>Kth Ancestor of node in a Binary tree</t></si><si><t>Find all Duplicate subtrees in a Binary tree [ IMP ]</t></si><si><t>Tree Isomorphism Problem</t></si><si><t>Binary Search Trees</t></si><si><t>Fina a value in a BST</t></si><si><t>Deletion of a node in a BST</t></si><si><t>Find min and max value in a BST</t></si><si><t>Find inorder successor and inorder predecessor in a BST</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Check if a tree is a BST or not </t></si><si><t>Populate Inorder successor of all nodes</t></si><si><t>Find LCA  of 2 nodes in a BST</t></si><si><t>Construct BST from preorder traversal</t></si><si><t>Convert Binary tree into BST</t></si><si><t>Convert a normal BST into a Balanced BST</t></si><si><t>Merge two BST [ V.V.V&gt;IMP ]</t></si><si><t>Find Kth largest element in a BST</t></si><si><t>Find Kth smallest element in a BST</t></si><si><t>Count pairs from 2 BST whose sum is equal to given value &quot;X&quot;</t></si><si><t>Find the median of BST in O(n) time and O(1) space</t></si><si><t>Count BST ndoes that lie in a given range</t></si><si><t>Replace every element with the least greater element on its right</t></si><si><t>Given &quot;n&quot; appointments, find the conflicting appointments</t></si><si><t>Check preorder is valid or not</t></si><si><t>Check whether BST contains Dead end</t></si><si><t>Largest BST in a Binary Tree [ V.V.V.V.V IMP ]</t></si><si><t>Flatten BST to sorted list</t></si><si><t>Greedy</t></si><si><t>Activity Selection Problem</t></si><si><t>Job SequencingProblem</t></si><si><t>Huffman Coding</t></si><si><t>Water Connection Problem</t></si><si><t>Fractional Knapsack Problem</t></si><si><t>Greedy Algorithm to find Minimum number of Coins</t></si><si><t>Maximum trains for which stoppage can be provided</t></si><si><t>Minimum Platforms Problem</t></si><si><t>Buy Maximum Stocks if i stocks can be bought on i-th day</t></si><si><t>Find the minimum and maximum amount to buy all N candies</t></si><si><t>Minimize Cash Flow among a given set of friends who have borrowed money from each other</t></si><si><t>Minimum Cost to cut a board into squares</t></si><si><t>Check if it is possible to survive on Island</t></si><si><t>Find maximum meetings in one room</t></si><si><t>Maximum product subset of an array</t></si><si><t>Maximize array sum after K negations</t></si><si><t>Maximize the sum of arr[i]*i</t></si><si><t>Maximum sum of absolute difference of an array</t></si><si><t>Maximize sum of consecutive differences in a circular array</t></si><si><t>Minimum sum of absolute difference of pairs of two arrays</t></si><si><t>Program for Shortest Job First (or SJF) CPU Scheduling</t></si><si><t>Program for Least Recently Used (LRU) Page Replacement algorithm</t></si><si><t>Smallest subset with sum greater than all other elements</t></si><si><t>Chocolate Distribution Problem</t></si><si><t>DEFKIN -Defense of a Kingdom</t></si><si><t>DIEHARD -DIE HARD</t></si><si><t>GERGOVIA -Wine trading in Gergovia</t></si><si><t>Picking Up Chicks</t></si><si><t>CHOCOLA –Chocolate</t></si><si><t>ARRANGE -Arranging Amplifiers</t></si><si><t>K Centers Problem</t></si><si><t>Minimum Cost of ropes</t></si><si><t>Find smallest number with given number of digits and sum of digits</t></si><si><t>Find maximum sum possible equal sum of three stacks</t></si><si><t>BackTracking</t></si><si><t>Rat in a maze Problem</t></si><si><t>Printing all solutions in N-Queen Problem</t></si><si><t>Word Break Problem using Backtracking</t></si><si><t>Remove Invalid Parentheses</t></si><si><t>Sudoku Solver</t></si><si><t>m Coloring Problem</t></si><si><t>Print all palindromic partitions of a string</t></si><si><t>Subset Sum Problem</t></si><si><t>The Knight’s tour problem</t></si><si><t>Tug of War</t></si><si><t>Find shortest safe route in a path with landmines</t></si><si><t>Combinational Sum</t></si><si><t>Find Maximum number possible by doing at-most K swaps</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Print all permutations of a string </t></si><si><t>Find if there is a path of more than k length from a source</t></si><si><t>Longest Possible Route in a Matrix with Hurdles</t></si><si><t>Print all possible paths from top left to bottom right of a mXn matrix</t></si><si><t>Partition of a set intoK subsets with equal sum</t></si><si><t>Find the K-th Permutation Sequence of first N natural numbers</t></si><si><t>Stacks &amp; Queues</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve"> Implement Stack from Scratch</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve"> Implement Queue from Scratch</t></si><si><t>Implement 2 stack in an array</t></si><si><t>find the middle element of a stack</t></si><si><t>Implement &quot;N&quot; stacks in an Array</t></si><si><t>Check the expression has valid or Balanced parenthesis or not.</t></si><si><t>Reverse a String using Stack</t></si><si><t>Design a Stack that supports getMin() in O(1) time and O(1) extra space.</t></si><si><t>Find the next Greater element</t></si><si><t>The celebrity Problem</t></si><si><t>Arithmetic Expression evaluation</t></si><si><t>Evaluation of Postfix expression</t></si><si><t>Implement a method to insert an element at its bottom without using any other data structure.</t></si><si><t>Reverse a stack using recursion</t></si><si><t>Sort a Stack using recursion</t></si><si><t>Merge Overlapping Intervals</t></si><si><t>Largest rectangular Area in Histogram</t></si><si><t>Length of the Longest Valid Substring</t></si><si><t>Expression contains redundant bracket or not</t></si><si><t>Implement Stack using Queue</t></si><si><t>Implement Stack using Deque</t></si><si><t>Stack Permutations (Check if an array is stack permutation of other)</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Implement Queue using Stack  </t></si><si><t>Implement &quot;n&quot; queue in an array</t></si><si><t>Implement a Circular queue</t></si><si><t>LRU Cache Implementationa</t></si><si><t>Reverse a Queue using recursion</t></si><si><t>Reverse the first “K” elements of a queue</t></si><si><t>Interleave the first half of the queue with second half</t></si><si><t>Find the first circular tour that visits all Petrol Pumps</t></si><si><t>Minimum time required to rot all oranges</t></si><si><t>Distance of nearest cell having 1 in a binary matrix</t></si><si><t>First negative integer in every window of size “k”</t></si><si><t>Check if all levels of two trees are anagrams or not.</t></si><si><t>Sum of minimum and maximum elements of all subarrays of size “k”.</t></si><si><t>Minimum sum of squares of character counts in a given string after removing “k” characters.</t></si><si><t>Queue based approach or first non-repeating character in a stream.</t></si><si><t>Next Smaller Element</t></si><si><t>Heap</t></si><si><t>Implement a Maxheap/MinHeap using arrays and recursion.</t></si><si><t>Sort an Array using heap. (HeapSort)</t></si><si><t>Maximum of all subarrays of size k.</t></si><si><t>“k” largest element in an array</t></si><si><t>Kth smallest and largest element in an unsorted array</t></si><si><t>Merge “K” sorted arrays. [ IMP ]</t></si><si><t>Merge 2 Binary Max Heaps</t></si><si><t>Kth largest sum continuous subarrays</t></si><si><t>Leetcode- reorganize strings</t></si><si><t>Merge “K” Sorted Linked Lists [V.IMP]</t></si><si><t>Smallest range in “K” Lists</t></si><si><t>Median in a stream of Integers</t></si><si><t>Check if a Binary Tree is Heap</t></si><si><t>Connect “n” ropes with minimum cost</t></si><si><t>Convert BST to Min Heap</t></si><si><t>Convert min heap to max heap</t></si><si><t>Rearrange characters in a string such that no two adjacent are same.</t></si><si><t>Minimum sum of two numbers formed from digits of an array</t></si><si><t>Graph</t></si><si><t>Create a Graph, print it</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Implement BFS algorithm </t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Implement DFS Algo </t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Detect Cycle in Directed Graph using BFS/DFS Algo </t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Detect Cycle in UnDirected Graph using BFS/DFS Algo </t></si><si><t>Search in a Maze</t></si><si><t>Minimum Step by Knight</t></si><si><t>flood fill algo</t></si><si><t>Clone a graph</t></si><si><t>Making wired Connections</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">word Ladder </t></si><si><t>Dijkstra algo</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Implement Topological Sort </t></si><si><t>Minimum time taken by each job to be completed given by a Directed Acyclic Graph</t></si><si><t>Find whether it is possible to finish all tasks or not from given dependencies</t></si><si><t>Find the no. of Isalnds</t></si><si><t>Given a sorted Dictionary of an Alien Language, find order of characters</t></si><si><t>Implement Kruksal’sAlgorithm</t></si><si><t>Implement Prim’s Algorithm</t></si><si><t>Total no. of Spanning tree in a graph</t></si><si><t>Implement Bellman Ford Algorithm</t></si><si><t>Implement Floyd warshallAlgorithm</t></si><si><t>Travelling Salesman Problem</t></si><si><t>Graph ColouringProblem</t></si><si><t>Snake and Ladders Problem</t></si><si><t>Find bridge in a graph</t></si><si><t>Count Strongly connected Components(Kosaraju Algo)</t></si><si><t>Check whether a graph is Bipartite or Not</t></si><si><t>Detect Negative cycle in a graph</t></si><si><t>Longest path in a Directed Acyclic Graph</t></si><si><t>Journey to the Moon</t></si><si><t>Cheapest Flights Within K Stops</t></si><si><t>Oliver and the Game</t></si><si><t>Water Jug problem using BFS</t></si><si><t>Find if there is a path of more thank length from a source</t></si><si><t>M-ColouringProblem</t></si><si><t>Minimum edges to reverse o make path from source to destination</t></si><si><t>Paths to travel each nodes using each edge(Seven Bridges)</t></si><si><t>Vertex Cover Problem</t></si><si><t>Chinese Postman or Route Inspection</t></si><si><t>Number of Triangles in a Directed and Undirected Graph</t></si><si><t>Minimise the cashflow among a given set of friends who have borrowed money from each other</t></si><si><t>Two Clique Problem</t></si><si><t>Trie</t></si><si><t>Construct a trie from scratch</t></si><si><t>Find shortest unique prefix for every word in a given list</t></si><si><t>Word Break Problem | (Trie solution)</t></si><si><t>Implement a Phone Directory</t></si><si><t>Print unique rows in a given boolean matrix</t></si><si><t>Dynamic Programming</t></si><si><t>Coin ChangeProblem</t></si><si><t>Knapsack Problem</t></si><si><t>Binomial CoefficientProblem</t></si><si><t>Permutation CoefficientProblem</t></si><si><t>Program for nth Catalan Number</t></si><si><t>Matrix Chain Multiplication </t></si><si><t>Edit Distance</t></si><si><t>Friends Pairing Problem</t></si><si><t>Gold Mine Problem</t></si><si><t>Assembly Line SchedulingProblem</t></si><si><t>Painting the Fenceproblem</t></si><si><t>Maximize The Cut Segments</t></si><si><t>Longest Common Subsequence</t></si><si><t>Longest Repeated Subsequence</t></si><si><t>Longest Increasing Subsequence</t></si><si><t>Space Optimized Solution of LCS</t></si><si><t>LCS (Longest Common Subsequence) of three strings</t></si><si><t>Maximum Sum Increasing Subsequence</t></si><si><t>Count all subsequences having product less than K</t></si><si><t>Longest subsequence such that difference between adjacent is one</t></si><si><t>Maximum subsequence sum such that no three are consecutive</t></si><si><t>Egg Dropping Problem</t></si><si><t>Maximum Length Chain of Pairs</t></si><si><t>Maximum size square sub-matrix with all 1s</t></si><si><t>Maximum sum of pairs with specific difference</t></si><si><t>Min Cost PathProblem</t></si><si><t>Maximum difference of zeros and ones in binary string</t></si><si><t>Minimum number of jumps to reach end</t></si><si><t>Minimum cost to fill given weight in a bag</t></si><si><t>Minimum removals from array to make max –min &lt;= K</t></si><si><t>Longest Common Substring</t></si><si><t>Count number of ways to reacha given score in a game</t></si><si><t>Count Balanced Binary Trees of Height h</t></si><si><t>LargestSum Contiguous Subarray [V&gt;V&gt;V&gt;V IMP ]</t></si><si><t>Smallest sum contiguous subarray</t></si><si><t>Unbounded Knapsack (Repetition of items allowed)</t></si><si><t>Word Break Problem</t></si><si><t>Largest Independent Set Problem</t></si><si><t>Partition problem</t></si><si><t>Longest Palindromic Subsequence</t></si><si><t>Count All Palindromic Subsequence in a given String</t></si><si><t>Longest Palindromic Substring</t></si><si><t>Longest alternating subsequence</t></si><si><t>Weighted Job Scheduling</t></si><si><t>Coin game winner where every player has three choices</t></si><si><t>Count Derangements (Permutation such that no element appears in its original position) [ IMPORTANT ]</t></si><si><t>Maximum profit by buying and selling a share at most twice [ IMP ]</t></si><si><t>Optimal Strategy for a Game</t></si><si><t>Optimal Binary Search Tree</t></si><si><t>Palindrome PartitioningProblem</t></si><si><t>Word Wrap Problem</t></si><si><t>Mobile Numeric Keypad Problem [ IMP ]</t></si><si><t>Boolean Parenthesization Problem</t></si><si><t>Largest rectangular sub-matrix whose sum is 0</t></si><si><t>Largest area rectangular sub-matrix with equal number of 1’s and 0’s [ IMP ]</t></si><si><t>Maximum sum rectangle in a 2D matrix</t></si><si><t>Maximum profit by buying and selling a share at most k times</t></si><si><t>Find if a string is interleaved of two other strings</t></si><si><t>Maximum Length of Pair Chain</t></si><si><t>Bit Manipulation</t></si><si><t>Count set bits in an integer</t></si><si><t>Find the two non-repeating elements in an array of repeating elements</t></si><si><t>Count number of bits to be flipped to convert A to B</t></si><si><t>Count total set bits in all numbers from 1 to n</t></si><si><t>Program to find whether a no is power of two</t></si><si><t>Find position of the only set bit</t></si><si><t>Copy set bits in a range</t></si><si><t>Divide two integers without using multiplication, division and mod operator</t></si><si><t>Calculate square of a number without using *, / and pow()</t></si><si><t>Power Set</t></si></sst>